{
    "subject": "resource/Forest_of_the_Hanged",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Forest of the Hanged is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9291430115699768,
            "question": "Is 'The Forest of the Hanged' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8655691742897034,
            "question": "What other types of films are similar to 'The Forest of the Hanged'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7394038438796997,
            "question": "Where was 'The Forest of the Hanged' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6843411922454834,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Forest of the Hanged'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6735829710960388,
            "question": "Would you recommend 'The Forest of the Hanged' to someone who enjoys [genre] films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5374057292938232,
            "question": "What is the general plot or theme of 'The Forest of the Hanged'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39869552850723267,
            "question": "What is the critical reception of 'The Forest of the Hanged'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38830655813217163,
            "question": "When was 'The Forest of the Hanged' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23725765943527222,
            "question": "Has 'The Forest of the Hanged' won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05556226149201393,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any famous actors or directors associated with this film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Forest of the Hanged is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6699_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'The Forest of the Hanged' won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6699_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Forest of the Hanged' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6699_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the critical reception of 'The Forest of the Hanged'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6699_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6699_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"Forest of the Hanged\" as a film, directed by Liviu Ciulei and released in 1964. Therefore, it supports the statement that \"The Forest of the Hanged is a type of Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}